siterapture.com 2018-05-09

# Privacy Policy - SiteRapture

SiteRapture.com (SR) aims to be the leading research and discovery service (social researching) bridging the gap between online consumers and the myriad of web-based products and services available to consumers. 

SiteRapture Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the SiteRapture.com Web site. No third parties are involved in these practices. This document was last updated on September 1, 2007.

Our site sends a cookie to track information such as your IP address and viewing habits. This cookie expires at the end of your user session, and does not need to be accepted to use our site. Advertisers may also offer cookies, for which we are not responsible; you do not need to accept any advertiser's cookie to use our site.

We use the information gathered from these cookies to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. It is also used to gather broad demographic information which we may share with partners including our Web hosting company, affiliated retailers and advertising partners. Our cookies do not track personally identifiable information, and so no personally identifiable information is ever released to our business partners.

Our site's newsletter registration form, feedback form or online surveys may require users to give us contact information (like name, zip code and e-mail address). These data are requested of, but not mandatory for, the user. Certain portions of SiteRapture content, however, may require user demographic data.

We use customer contact information from the newsletter registration form and surveys (but not the feedback form) to send the user information about and reports issued by our company, via our newsletter. This newsletter is issued no more frequently than once every two weeks. Users may opt out of receiving future mailings through a procedure included in every newsletter; see the Choice/Opting Out section below. The demographic and profile information collected at our site is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis only. Should we change our policy on handling personally identifiable information, we will notify you by e-mail and post the change on this site.

This site contains links to other sites. SiteRapture.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Please review the privacy policies of each individual site for more information.

If this privacy policy should change in the future with respect to how we handle personally identifiable information or e-mail addresses, we will e-mail all e-mail addresses affected by the change.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Most data is kept on an aggregate basis only, so that no personal data is available on a user-by-user basis. Our mailing list information is kept on a password-protected FTP server separate from our Web server. We do use a Web-hosting service to process our information, but the company does not access or use this information except on an aggregate basis.

**Choice/Opting Out**

Whenever we request information or contact data from the user, we provide the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us. No business partners of ours are permitted to contact our users directly at this point. To remove your user information from our database or not receive further communication from our Web site, send e-mail to michael@SiteRapture.com.

**Correct/Update**

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. To correct or update your information, send e-mail to michael@SiteRapture.com.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

SiteRapture, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Policy Team  
5482 Wilshire Blvd. #419  
Los Angeles, CA 90036  
info@siterapture.com
